# JACKY ANDRAZAT

#### **Programer**

Jakarta | +62 81350633907 | jackyandrazat@gmail.com | Linkedin | Github

#### **RINGKASAN**

a programmer who has a vocational school educational background and Padang State Polytechnic Information Technology Department, who strengthens his understanding of software development, technological advances and analytical skills and is proficient in various programming languages, with several experiences in companies and organizations. Ready to contribute to the company and team as well as high dedication to professional growth, good communication skills and deep understanding of the software development cycle.

#### **PENDIDIKAN**

# 1. FORMAL EDUCATION POLITEKNIK NEGERI PADANG

SEPTEMBER 2020 - AGUSTUS 2023

D3 MANAJEMEN INFORMATIKA - IPK . 3.57

- Learn Supporting Theories for IT Majors
- Learn Basic Programing With C
- Learn SQL Basics
- Learn SQL Fundamentals and Queries
- Learn HTML CSS and Javascript
- Learn Java Basics
- Created Website With HTML CSS and Javascript
- create a Library Application with Netbeans and Java language
- Learn PHP Basic Fundamentals and Experts
- Create an Employee Website with PHP Native and Bootstrap
- Learn Basic Mobile Dev with Android Study using Java
- Learn the PHP Laravel Framework
- Creating CRUD websites with Laravel
- Creating a Simple Cashier Application with .Net and SQL Server
- Learn Basic GIS and ARCGis.
- Learn Basic Enterprise Applications with Odoo Enterprise
- Creating a Population Information System Final Project with Laravel

AGUSTUS 2022 - DESEMBER 2022	2. Study Independent Kampus Merdeka x Dicoding Academy FRONT END BACKEND WEB DEVELOPER			
	<ul> <li>Introduction to Programming Logic (Programming Logic 101)</li> <li>Learn Programming Basics to Become a Software Developer</li> <li>Learn JavaScript Programming Basics</li> <li>Learn Module Pemograman Web Dasar</li> <li>Learn Basic Github</li> <li>Learn to Create a Web Front-End for Beginners</li> <li>Learn the Fundamentals of Front-End Web Development</li> <li>Become a Front-End Web Developer Expert</li> <li>Learning Computer Networks for Beginners</li> <li>Learn to Create Back-End Applications for Beginners</li> <li>Create Capstone Project Front End Blog Information Parenting Family (Pafa)</li> </ul>			
2017 -2020	<ol> <li>SMK Adi Karya Ranah Pesisir Pesisir Selatan Rekayasa Perangkaat Lunak (RPL)</li> </ol>			
	<ul> <li>Learning Normative Material</li> <li>Learning Adaptive Material</li> <li>Learning Productive Material with vocational competence in Computer Networks, Java Netbeands Programming, Visual Basic, HTML CSS PHP Website Programming.</li> </ul>			
July 2021 - Agustus 2021	4. Non Formal Education VSGA Digitalent Kominfo			
	<ul> <li>Learning about Junior Web Developer tips and HTML CSS Javascript as well as practical implementation of creating a website page.</li> <li>Learning Basics PHP</li> <li>Learning Bootstrap and Implementation</li> <li>Basic CRUD with PHP</li> </ul>			

5. AWS Back End Academy	Maret 2024 - Sekarang
<ul> <li>Learning Basic AWS</li> <li>Learn JavaScript Programming Basics</li> <li>Learn to Create Back-End Applications for Beginners</li> </ul>	

#### **EXPERIENCE**

PT METEOR INOVASI DIGITAL

Februari 2023 - Juni 2023

Position: INTERN

#### **IT Product Management**

- Product research.
- Defining product strategy and roadmap.
- Handle product issues.
- Determine detailed product specifications.

#### IT Business Analyst

- Gather business requirements from various departments and stakeholders.
- Analysis and decomposition of business needs into requirements that can be understood by the IT development team. Designing information technology solutions that can meet business needs.
- Make detailed business analysis, describe problems, and provide solutions to develop the business.
- Understand customer needs and business goals.
- Write all requirements into the BRD document.

#### **Fullstack Developer**

- Slicing Design using HTML and Tailwind CSS.
- Tailwind CSS HTML Project Configuration with Github and Netlify.
- Creating a Web Front End with React JS and Tailwind CSS and Using the Daisy UI Package and Fake API and Mobile Responsive, Local Storage.
- Creating a Web Back End with Express JS and Node JS with MVC, Token, Auth, Encryption.
- Creating API and Connecting Backend with Front End using AXIOS.
- Doing a test with Postman.

### **Quality Assurance**

- Testing Company Project Portal Applications and Websites based on Test Scenarios from the Senior QA team.
- Create Test Scenarios and request approval from the Senior QA team for the Test Scenarios created.

#### FREELANCE PROGRAMER

Position: FREELANCE

# Landing Page School Madrasah Tsanawiwah Muhammadiyah Lakitan Kabupaten Pesisir Selatan

 Creating Landing Page Web With HTML Tailwind CSS.

**CRUD Task Laravel** Desember 2022

- Implementation Dashboard Theme
- Code and Feature CRUD Improvements
- Adding Feature Report PDF EXCEL Etc.

# Kelompok Penyelenggara Pemungutan Suara (KPPS) 2024

Position: KPPS 5

KPPS Work Briefing.

- KPPS Inauguration and Seminar.
- Sirekap Admin.
- Providing information on the use of Sirekap.
- Recording and adjusting voter data and attendance lists based on data from KPPS 4 (Pantarlih).
- Upload Data to Sirekap.
- Report.

# PT TRASINDO DATA PERKASA / JASAMEDIKA TRANSMEDIC

Position: Programmer Site / Web Developer Site at RSCM CIPTO MANGUNKUSUMO Jakarta Central

- Development of Features or User Requests for RSCM and Implementation of the Transmedi Hospital Management Information System (SIMRS) Application
- Fixed Bug in SIMRS
- Created Front End with Vue JS, and used Vuero, PrimeVue and Bulma packages

Oktober 2023

Desember 2023 - Februari 2024

**April 2024 - Now** 

- Playing Database Query calls for Backend With Laravel,
- Handling the Pharmacy and administration module, logistics, bank eye, emr in SIMRS by handling the Print feature, and several Front End Feature modules for pharmacy, admission, logistics and get data with Database queries to be combined with the backend and displayed on the front end.

Position: Programmer/ Web Developerat RSPPN Panglima Besar Soedirman, South Jakarta

- assisting development for go-live simrs transmedic in rsspn by working on emr module and printing form or data in all module.
- responding if there is a bug report.

#### SKILL

SOFT SKILL	:	TIME MANAGEMENT, CRITICAL THINKING, PROBLEM SOLVING, LEADERSHIP, TEAMWORK AND PUBLIC SPEAKING.
HARD SKILL	:	HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, LARAVEL, MYSQL, JQUERY, REACT JS, INERTIA, AJAX, BOOTSTRAP, TAILWIND, C, C#, JAVA, GIT, VITE, NODE JS, EXPRES JS, GIT, AXIOS, API, UI/UX, VUERO, PRIMEVUE, BULMA CSS.
SOFTWARE SKILL	:	MS OFFICE, GITHUB, VS CODE , VS COMUNITY, VB BASIC, FIGMA, CANVA, POSTMAN, XAMPP, NETBEANS, AWS, Netlify, LINUX.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

- 1. Pemograman Web Dasar <u>Dicoding Indonesia</u>
- 2. Dasar Github Dicoding Indonesia Kodekloud
- 3. Jaringan Komputer Dicoding Indonesia
- 4. Pemrograman Software Developer Dicoding Indonesia
- 5. Javascript Dasar Dicoding Indonesia
- 6. Front End Pemula Dicoding Indonesia
- 7. Front End Fundamental Dicoding Indonesia
- 8. Font End Expert Dicoding Indonesia
- 9. Backend Pemula Dicoding Indonesia
- 10. Junior Web Developer.